<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Dipam Chakraborty</title>
        <link>http://example.org/</link>
        <description>Dipam Chakraborty&#39;s homepage</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>chakraborty.dipam@gmail.com (Dipam Chakraborty)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>chakraborty.dipam@gmail.com (Dipam Chakraborty)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>About me</title>
    <link>http://example.org/about/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/about/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;m Dipam, a technology enthusiast, science nerd, and lover of food and travel.
I&rsquo;m currently working as a machine learning engineer at AIcrowd Research. Primarily, I work on hosting research oriented competitions, especially focussed on reinforcement learning. AIcrowd has hosted many research competitions in machine and reinforcement learning. In fact, I joined AIcrowd after winning 3rd position in the NeurIPS 2020 Procgen competition hosted there. I&rsquo;ve contributed heavily to the NeurIPS 2022 Citylearn Challenge, Multi Agent Behavior Challenge 2022, ZEW Data Purchasing Challenge, NeurIPS 2021 Deepracer Challenge, Flatland 3, and Multi Agent Behavior Challenge 2021.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Thoughts on the ARC Benchmark</title>
    <link>http://example.org/thoughts-on-the-arc-benchmark/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 16:29:41 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://example.org/thoughts-on-the-arc-benchmark/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Notes on the ARC benchmark, my experience at the competition, and how it can become a long-term benchmark in AI - Twitter Thread
The ARC Benchmark Around the end of 2019, François Chollet released the Abstraction and Reasoning Corpus (ARC) benchmark, along with the paper On the Measure of Intelligence. And in the paper, he made a powerful claim: that deep learning cannot solve the ARC benchmark.
On the surface, the tasks in the benchmark are simple.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
